

Mohamed JELLALI FULLSTACK JS WEB DEVELOPER ENGINEER

6.

+216 21 462 167



mohamedjjellali@gmail.com



Ezzouhour, Tunis, Tunisie



14/02/1992



LinkedIN: Mohamed JELLALI



GitHub: MohamedIELLALI



https://mohamed-jellali.her okuapp.com/

"Hi! I am Mohamed, a fullstack web engineer, and previously an automotive quality management engineer.

I am very passionate about Web Development, and strive to better myself as a developer, and the development community as a whole.

Actually I specialize in javascript MERN stack."

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Web Development | 2020-2021

• GoMyCode: Fullstack JS MERN Web Development

Engineering Cycle | 2012-2015

National Engineering School of Monastir « ENIM »:
 National Engineer Diploma in Mechanical Engineering

Preparatory Engineering Cycle | 2010 - 2012

• Preparatory Engineering Institute of El Manar

WORK EXPERIENCE

GoMyCode | FULLSTACK JS Instructor (Part Time) | april 2021- Now

° Train students on the MERN STACK: Ensure that the students understand the technical aspects of each technology and expand their soft skills through active learning.

GoMyCode | FULLSTACK JS MERN | Aug 2020 - Feb2021

- * WeEvent.com (MERN Stack) : Development of a website that allows athletes to create and participate in sports events (Frontend & Backend).
- * Marvel App (MERN Stack + Docker + Marvel API) : Development of a web application with Marvel API (Frontend & Backend).
- ° Chat Application: Frontend: React Js + Backend: Chat Engine.
- ° My Portfolio Website: Frontend: React Js, Deployment: Heroku.
- ° Users Management App (Node JS + Express JS + Mongoose) : Management of user data through a web application (Backend).
- * **Devices Management App** (Angular+Firebase) : A web Application That manages the electrical devices (Frontend & Backend).

VALEO | Quality Team Leader (PSA)| Feb 2020- Nov2020

- ° Represent the site in the meetings, visits and confcalls with the top management and the customer (PSA).
- ° Animate quality daily meetings: Coaching the team, review of KPIs.

VALEO | Customer Quality Engineer (PSA) | Aug 2017 - Feb 2020

- ° Resolve customer and warranty quality issues.
- ° Design and implement the quality procedures.

BONTAZ | Production Engineer | May 2016 - Aug 2017

° Lead the continuous improvement projects and validate working methods

SKILLS

FUNCTIONAL

- Responsive web application
- Clean and maintainable code
- Git workflow
- Troubleshooting

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Team player
- Adaptability
- Quick learner
- Organization
- Time and stress management

TECHNOLOGIES

• FRONT-END:

React, Redux, Angular, Javascript, Typescript, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML.

• BACK-END:

NODE JS, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, SQL.

OTHERS:

GIT/GitHub, Docker, Axios, Visual Studio, Matlab, Turbo Pascal, UML Conception, MySQL, PUG, Json, Postman.

LANGUAGES

ARAB FRENCH ENGLISH







